http://www.stjohnshartford.org/privacy-notice

Church Member Login
Register
HomeAbout usIntroducing St John'sNew here?Who's whoMission LinksHistoryChurch HistoryChurch ExtensionGuided TourVicars of HartfordParish MagazinesFamily History ResearchChurch CentreBooking EnquiryFacilitiesThe CrossBuilding the CentreRecruitmentWhat's onSt John's this weekChurch on SundayWeddings & BaptismsWeddingsBaptismsThe Marriage CourseWomen's GroupsMen's GroupsGroups for AdultsCalendarFaithWhat is a Christian?Learning MoreSermon RecordingsOnline ServicesDaily DevotionsSt John's PodcastsReading the BibleYoung PeopleChildren & Young People at St John'sBirth to 4 yearsAges 5 to 11Ages 11 to 18SchoolsSchools Ministry at St John'sSchool At Home ResourcesFor TeachersHartford Church of England High SchoolGetting InvolvedContactContact usMap and Directions
Privacy Notice
Home
Privacy Notice
Register
Church Member Login
Data Privacy Notice & Cookie Policy
Data Privacy Notice
The PCC (Parochial Church Council) has agreed a Data Privacy Policy in order to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). If you choose to give St John's any personal data, it will be processed and stored in accordance with this policy.
You can download and read the Data Privacy Notice (PDF document, will open in a new tab or window).
No personal data is processed through your use of this website, unless you choose to sign up for access to the Church Members' Area. If you register, the information you provide to create your account is only used to provide access to the members' area.
Cookie Policy
Our website uses cookies, as almost all websites do, to help the site work properly and efficiently. Cookies are small files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone when you browse websites. We use cookies for the follow reasons:
to make our website work properly;
to save you having to login every time you visit the Members area of the site;
to remember whether you wish to view the Mobile or Full Desktop version of the site;
providing anonymous statistics such as the number of visitors, popular pages and broken links, allowing us to continually improve the site.
We will never use cookies to collect any personally identifiable or sensitive information, pass data to advertisers or pass personally identifiable data to any third parties. You can read specific detail about all the cookies we use below.
Granting us permission to use cookies
If the settings on the browser that you are using to view this website are adjusted to accept cookies we take this, and your continued use of our website, to mean that you are fine with this. Should you wish to remove or not use cookies from our site you can learn how to do this below, however doing so will mean that parts of our site will not work as you would expect.
More about our Cookies
Functional Cookies
We use cookies to make our website work properly:
Temporary "session" cookies that make our site work (these are destroyed as soon as you leave our site and close your browser);
A cookie that is set to remember your choice between the mobile and desktop versions of our website. You will only receive this cookie if you visit the mobile site and then select to view the full site;
A cookie that allows you to login and determines if you are already logged in or not.
There is no way to prevent these cookies being set other than to not use our site.
Third party functions
Our site, in common with most modern websites, includes functionality provided by third parties. For example, we use Google Calendar for the church calendar and YouTube (run by Google) for videos. Google will set cookies when you use these functions. Disabling these cookies will probably break the functions offered by these third parties. Our contact, login and registration forms use security checks provided by Google - a logo is visible in the bottom left of your screen when these are active. This logo has links to Google's privacy policies.
Anonymous Visitor Statistics Cookies
We use Google Analytics to collect anonymous statistics about how our site is used. Google Analytics allows us, for example, to track the number of visits to our site, to see which pages are popular, to see if any links are broken and to see what search terms people use when they find our site.
None of the information collected allows us to personally identify you. Google will set cookies in order for their service to work. You can read Google's privacy policies in more detail.
Turning Cookies Off
You can usually switch cookies off by adjusting your browser settings to stop it from accepting cookies. This is not recommended, because doing so will break some parts of this site and you will experience problems with other websites. Please remember that cookies are a standard part of most modern websites.
Contacting
us
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
St John's this weekAre you new here?What is a Christian?St John's Church CentreSermon RecordingsYoung PeopleContact us
